<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<doc>
  <title auto="true" type="str" verify="true"><![CDATA[Shelter (Официальный сайт, информация о персонажах, текст песни) и другое]]></title>
  <author auto="true" type="str" verify="true"><![CDATA[Shadow0110]]></author>
  <categories auto="true" type="list" verify="true">
    <category type="str"><![CDATA[Аниме]]></category>
  </categories>
  <keywords auto="true" type="list" verify="true"/>
  <date auto="true" type="datetime" verify="true"><![CDATA[2016-10-19T23:49:27+03:00]]></date>
  <text auto="true" type="str" verify="true"><![CDATA[Введение (вся информация с этого сайта  sheltertheanimation.com/ )    Musician and producer, Porter Robinson, known for his emotional electronic music and a penchant for incorporating iconic visuals in his work, presents his latest integration of both in "Shelter" the video. A long time fan of Japanese pop culture, he teamed up with Japanese animation powerhouse, "A-1 Pictures" to create a moving story for his shimmering new collaborative single, "Shelter," with his close friend and fellow musician, Madeon.  История    Rin, a 17-year-old girl, lives inside a futuristic simulator in infinite, beautiful loneliness. Each day, she awakens in virtual reality to create a world for herself, yet in real life, Rin’s comatose body floats through the universe, forever trapped inside a virtual simulation she will never wake up from...  О персонажах   RIN   A 17-year-old girl. Trapped in her beautiful, yet lonely days, she begins to wonder about the outside world, and why she is all alone.       SHIGERU     A Japanese scientist and engineer.     Музыка     Исполнитель   Porter Robinson & Madeon (ポーター・ロビンソン＆マデオン)   Musicians and longtime friends Porter Robinson and Madeon each made a name for themselves as solo artists and producers-producers who redefined electronic music from the inside out, expanding the genre from the festival stage to the pop charts and bringing electronic music into the global mainstream. SHELTER (シェルター )   “Shelter”- a brilliant shimmering, humanity-infused electronic pop - comes at a serendipitous time for the two young artists and sees the duo taking a hands-on approach to the songwriting process. To write, the two decamped to Madeon’s studio in Nantes, France and the two wrote together in real-time, face-to-face, taking a decidedly old-school approach to the collaboration, inspiring and challenging one-another along the way. The result, “Shelter” is an ode to family ties as much as it’s a pop song that epitomizes their friendship. Текст песни     На Английском  спойлер "I could never find the right way to tell you, have you noticed I've been gone? Because I left behind the home that you made me, but I will carry it along. Mm, it's a long way forward, so trust in me. I'll give them shelter like you've done for me, and I know I'm not alone, you'll be watching over us. Until you're gone. When I'm older I'll be silent beside you, I know words won't be enough. And they won't need to know our names or our faces, but they will carry on for us. Mm, it's a long way forward, so trust in me. I'll give them shelter like you've done for me, and I know I'm not alone, you'll be watching over us. Until you're gone." На японском  спойлер なかなか上手く伝えられなかったけど、 僕がいなくなっている事に気づいてた？ 僕のためにつくってくれた家を出てしまったから それでも伝えていくよ まだ先は長いから 僕を信じて きみがしてくれたように　彼らにもシェルターを与えるよ 独りじゃないって 僕たちを見守ってくれるんだね きみが消えてしまうまで 僕が年をとったらきみのそばで静かにしている 言葉だけじゃ足りない 彼らは僕たちの名前も顔も知らなくていい それでも伝えていってくれるから まだ先は長いから 僕を信じて きみがしてくれたように　彼らにもシェルターを与えるよ 独りじゃないって 僕たちを見守ってくれるんだね きみが消えてしまうまで Персонал   Executive Producer / WriterPorter Robinson   спойлер Musician, composer, creator, who first caught the ears of tastemakers in 2010 with his track “Say My Name.” An EP on Skrillex’s OWSLA label followed and he signed to the venerated Astralwerks in 2013 when he was all of 21. The next year he released his debut artist album, Worlds, which debuted in Billboard’s Top 20. Director Toshifumi Akai     спойлер Animator, character designer, director who's notable works include "Sound of the Sky," "Magi: The Labyrinth of Magic" (character designer and chief animation director), "Kokoro Connect" (character design), "THE  [email protected]  CINDERELLA GIRLS" (animation director, storyboard, direction, original sketch), etc. Most recently, he has been involved in the character design for "GRANBLUE FANTASY The Animation."   Character Design Megumi Kouno     спойлер Notable works include "THE  [email protected]  CINDERELLA GIRLS" (chief animation director), "Vividred Operation" (key animator), "KILL la KILL," "Sword Art Online," "One-Punch Man," (original sketch) etc. "SHELTER" will be Kouno's first project as character designer. Art Direction Yusuke Takeda     спойлер Signed to Bamboo Inc., his notable works include "Ghost in the Shell: STAND ALONE COMPLEX," "BLOOD THE LAST VAMPIRE," "Guilty Crown," "Sword Art Online", "The Empire of Corpses," etc. He has also worked on many other projects as art director. В ролях В роли Rin:Sachika Misawa       спойлер Voice actress whose notable works include "Accel World" (Kuroyukihime), "Locodol"(Yukari Kohinata), "Aldnoah.Zero" (Rayet Areash), etc.]]></text>
</doc>
