<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<doc>
  <title auto="true" type="str" verify="true"><![CDATA[Kuzu no Honkai - Valentine's Special Voice video]]></title>
  <author auto="true" type="str" verify="true"><![CDATA[Dark_zarich]]></author>
  <categories auto="true" type="list" verify="true">
    <category type="str"><![CDATA[Аниме]]></category>
  </categories>
  <keywords auto="true" type="list" verify="true"/>
  <date auto="true" type="datetime" verify="true"><![CDATA[2017-02-12T01:41:34+03:00]]></date>
  <text auto="true" type="str" verify="true"><![CDATA[10 февраля на официальном сайте аниме  Kuzu no Honkai  появились специальные видео, которые озвучили сейю персонажей для фанатов сериала по случаю Дня Святого Валентина. Приняли участие: Chika Anzai  -  CV   Hanabi Yasuraoka Haruka Tomatsu  -  CV   Sanae Ebato Shiori Izawa  -  CV   Noriko Kamomebata Aki Toyosaki  -  CV   Akane Minagawa youtube youtube youtube Перевод на английский от пользователей сайта  reddit : Hanabi Yasuraoka : "Good work today. Sorry to call you out like this. I guess it's a little conspicuous.Tada! This year I made you a ganache tart! Huh? I didn't go overboard, it's just normal. I don't mind making things from scratch. Every year I try a new recipe. I know I say this every year, but onii-chan, happy Valentine's Day!"   Sanae Ebato : "Good work today. Huh? I didn't follow you! I told you I had something to give you today, didn't I? So... I gave these out to everyone in class today too, but I brought you some chocolate. No... haha... I didn't go overboard, I just thought it would be fun to make something. Really! Alright, alright, stop asking! Here, happy Valentine's Day." Noriko Kamomebata : "You came after all! ...No, I didn't wait, not at all... Hey, this is... Valentine chocolate... Huh? It's too cute? Is that not okay? ..A-Are you happy? Truly? hehehe I, too, am happy! Happy Valentine's day!" Akane Minagawa : "Good work today. Sorry to have you come to the music room. Sensei, you've probably already received some chocolate from other female students, right? I might be a little jealous. Would you accept mine too? Happy Valentine's Day." источник:  www.kuzunohonkai.com]]></text>
</doc>
